Javad dehghan

Software Engineer (Front-End)

- ↑ Karaj
- +989367640954
- 📩 javad.amindehghan1@gmail.com

personal website

https://javadamindehghan.github.io/resume/

SUMMARY

mid-level front-end developer with over 2 years of experience in designing and building responsive websites with a beautiful user interface. Successful experience in front-end development using the React JS library, through participation in over 5 projects. Notable achievements include increased project completion speed and improved website conversion rates with enhanced code and design.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Mid-level React Developer 📍 Tehran

karkhone-digital, LA, Remote 2022 -2024

- Software Engineering startup company with 100+ employ
- During my tenure as a front-end developer at <u>karkhone-digital</u>, I contributed to the

development of over three websites catering to a wide range of industries,

- including social media, e-commerce, and other web-based projects.
- Developed and launched three highly engaging websites to drive product
- and service awareness, resulting in a 40% increase in organic website traffic
- and a 25% boost in lead generation within the first quarter.
- Implemented a cutting-edge technology stack, utilizing React, Next.js,
 Redux
- Toolkit, and Graphql, resulting in a substantial 50% boost in team
- productivity by accelerating feature development, reducing bugs, and
- enhancing user experience.

Junior React Developer 📍 Karaj

Tara, On site 2021 - 2022

- Startup company, manufacturing smart tools for agricultural purposes
- Implemented cutting-edge front-end designs and optimized user interfaces, resulting in a 50%
- reduction in page load time and a 20% increase in website traffic conversions.
- Through my contributions, we were able to achieve significant growth, with a 20% increase in
- revenue within a year.
- My development skills improved significantly as I worked on these projects, and I had the
- · opportunity to collaborate with a colleague/friend on one project, which helped me develop my
- teamwork abilities in addition to my individual skills.
- Successfully performing maintenance on the front-end of the platform, which is based on HTML,
- ¡Query and React
- Strong believer in the mantra that we learn from our mistakes.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Civil EngineeringGhiasodin University

? Qazvin 2011 - 2015

SKILLS

TypeScript, JavaScript (ES5, ES6, ES7), PHP, HTML/CSS/SCSS
React JS, React Query, Webpack
Redux, Redux-toolkit
Bootstrap, Tailwindcss MUI-Kit (Material ui)
Styled-components
Formik, yup, React-Hook-Form
Experience with RestFull and GraphqIPWA, Web & Service Workers, Web Sockets, CSS Modules
JsDoc & Clean Code
Github, Gitlab
Adobe XD, Figma
Npm,Pnpm,Yarn
Git&Github-Gitlab

Soft Skills:

Articulating communication
Intermediate in English
Planning
Honest
Responsible
Creative
Good mannered
Eagerness to learn new and Update concepts
having a team spirit
Not afraid of failure